thedoctorstv.com 2018-06-30

# The Doctors Privacy Policy | The Doctors TV Show

**The Doctors**  
 **Privacy Policy**

Last Updated and Effective as of: APRIL 9, 2018

This Privacy Policy applies only to TheDoctorsTV.com (however accessed and/or used, whether via personal computers, mobile devices, or otherwise), or other interactive features accessible or downloadable through TheDoctorsTV.com that are owned or controlled by Stage 29 Productions, LLC (“Company,” “we,” “our” or “us”) and that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Web Site”). This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at the Web Site, and does not cover any information collected at any other web site or offline by Company (unless specifically stated). This Privacy Policy describes, among other things, the types of information collected about you when you visit the Web Site; how your information may be used and when it may be disclosed; how you can control the use and disclosure of your information; and how your information is protected.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. In addition, please review our [Terms of Use](https://www.thedoctorstv.com/terms-of-use "Terms of Use"), which govern your use of the Web Site and any content you submit to the Web Site, and our Video Services Policy, which describes how in some circumstances third parties may have access to information about what videos you have watched on the [Web Site](https://www.thedoctorstv.com/ "Web Site"). **   **

 _ **PRIVACY POLICY OVERVIEW**_  
Please review our full privacy policy below – but here are some key points to know:

  * We may collect information about you in a variety of ways, including: when you provide information to us directly,automatically as you use the Web Site, and from third-party sources.  
 
  * We primarily use the information collected from you in order to allow you to participate in the Web Site and to communicate information and offers to you (on the Web Site and elsewhere online). We may share your personal information under certain limited circumstances, such as with vendors providing services to us or for legal compliance. We may also share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes where you have consented to such sharing. For more details, click here. California residents should also review the "Your California Privacy Rights"section of this policy **.**  
 
  * We work with third-party service providers, including CBS Interactive, to serve and analyze advertisements on the Web Site and elsewhere online and to provide us with information regarding use of the Web Site. Analytics providers, ad network providers, ad agencies, advertisers and similar third parties may set and access their own tracking devices (including cookies and web beacons) and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you and your visits to the Web Site or other online services. Such information may be used to display targeted ads to you. For more information, including opt-out options that may be available to you, please review the “Third-Party Ad Serving & Audience and Traffic Measurement Services” section below.  
 
  * When you view video content on the Web Site, share information through a social-networking feature on the Web Site, or post to one of the Web Site’s Public Areas, third parties may have access to information on what videos you have watched.  For more information, please see our Video Services [Policy](https://legalterms.cbsinteractive.com/video-services).  
 
  * We have adopted commercially reasonable procedures to help protect your information, but please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  

**_**TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED**_  
The following are the types of information we may collect:**

 ** **Information You Provide to Us****  
We may ask you to provide us with information through the Web Site, including the following: 

  * Personal information, which is information that could reasonably be used to identify you as a specific person, such as your name, e-mail address, cell phone number, and physical address;   
 
  * Demographic information, such as gender, zip code, information regarding your education or number of children, or similar information; and  
 
  * Other information about yourself, such as your interests or preferences.  
 
  * You may also be asked to choose a user name and password in order to identify yourself during future visits to the Web Site. Do not use your real name or the name of any other actual person as your user name.

We may combine non-personal information with personal information, in which case we will treat the combined information as personal information under this Privacy Policy. 

Providing us with information about yourself is your choice, and you can always choose not to provide certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of some of the Web Site’s features.

Note that we may de-identify personal information we have received, turning it into non-personal information. This is sometimes accomplished using a mathematical process (commonly known as a hash function) to convert information into a code. The code does not identify you directly, but it may be used to connect your activity and interests.

 **Information We Collect Automatically on the Web Site**

 ** **We may collect information automatically when you visit the Web Site, including: ********

  * ****Information about your device, including device type and settings, and browser type and operating system;****
  * ****Web sites or other services you visited before and after visiting the Web Site;****
  * ****Areas of the Web Site with which you interact, advertisements you view, and links you click on within the Web Site;****
  * ****Your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which is a number automatically assigned to your device whenever you access the Internet, or another unique identifier for the device you use to access the Web Site (e.g. Apple’s Identifier for Advertising (IDFA) or Google’s Android Advertising ID (AAID)).   IP address can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area.****
  * ****Information about your internet connection (e.g., mobile operator, ISP, WiFi connection).****
  * ****Information collected throughcookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies.****
  * ******Information about your interactions with email messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or forwarded.******

******When analyzed, this usage information helps us determine how visitors arrive at the Web Site, what type of content is most popular, what type of content you may find most relevant and what type of visitors are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising.******

 **Information from Other Sources**  
We may receive information about you from other sources. For example, we may obtain geographic or demographic information, or information regarding your possible interests, from third parties, or we may receive information from a marketing partner in connection with a co-branded web site or promotion. We may use this information for a variety of purposes, including to enhance our ability to serve you and to tailor content and ads we serve to you. We may combine the information we receive from those other sources with information we collect through the Web Site. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to any personal information received, unless otherwise specifically disclosed by us at the time you provide your personal information

Send to a Friend  
If you send a friend a communication from the Web Site, the information you provide (names, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, etc.) is used on a one-time basis to facilitate the communication and is not used for any other marketing purpose, unless we obtain additional consent from that person.

Return to Top

 _ **METHODS WE MAY USE TO COLLECT INFORMATION**_

 **Cookies**  
The Web Site uses standard technology called “cookies,” which are small data files that are transferred to your device when you visit the Web Site, if your browser is set to accept cookies. Cookies automatically identify your web browser to the Web Site whenever you visit the Web Site, and may make navigating and using the Web Site easier for you and allow you to personalize your experience on the Web Site. If you do not want to allow information to be collected through the use of cookies, you can generally opt out of providing this information by setting your browser to reject cookies. However, please be aware that some areas of the Web Site may not provide you with an acceptable user experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.

 **Web Beacons**  
The Web Site and any communications sent by the Web Site may contain electronic images (generally, single-pixel “.gif” images) called “web beacons.” These web beacons allow Company and third parties to monitor and collect certain information about the viewer of the web page, web-based document, e-mail message, or other communication, such as the type of browser requesting the web beacon, a unique identifier of the device that the web beacon is sent to and the time the web beacon was viewed. 

**Embedded Scripts**  
An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Web Site, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your device from our server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Web Site, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

In addition, we may use a variety of other technologies that collect similar information for security and fraud detection purposes.

Return to Top

 _ **DO NOT TRACK**_  
 ** ** **Some Internet browsers include the ability to transmit “Do Not Track” signals. Since uniform standards for “Do Not Track” signals have not been adopted, this Web Site does not process or respond to “Do Not Track” signals. To learn more about “Do Not Track,” please visit “All About Do Not Track” at www.allaboutdnt.com/.******

 ** ** **Return to Top******

 _ **HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED**_  
 ** ** **The information we collect may be used to:******

  *  ** ** **Provide you with electronic newsletters, information, special offers and promotional materials on behalf of us or third parties;******
  * ******Fulfill your requests for products, services, and information and complete a transaction that you have requested;******
  * ******Enable you to participate in Web Site features, such as surveys, polls, sweepstakes/contests, and Public Areas (defined below);******
  * ******Contact you about the Web Site, including, without limitation, in our discretion to notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy, the Web Site’s Terms of Use, or other policies that affect your use of the Web Site;******
  * ******Analyze the use of Web Site and information about visitors to our Web Site to understand and improve our service offerings and for other internal business purposes;******
  * ******Customize the advertising and content you see, both on the Web Site and elsewhere online;******
  * ******Comply with and monitor compliance with our Terms of Use and other applicable agreements and polices;******
  * ******Evaluate you for a possible invitation to be a guest on The Doctors Show;******
  * ******Generate topics for The Doctors Show;******
  * ******Determine whether we may offer you a reservation to be an audience member at The Doctors Show; and******
  * ******For other purposes disclosed when you provide your information.******

******Please note that information submitted to the Web Site via a   “Contact Us,” or other similar mechanism will not necessarily receive a response. We will not use any such information you provide for marketing purposes unrelated to your request, although we may contact you regarding your submission or being a guest on The Doctors Show. ******

******Return to Top******

 _ **WITH WHOM INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED**_  
 ** ** **We may share information collected about you as disclosed at the time of collection, as otherwise disclosed in this privacy policy, and in the following circumstances:******

 **With your Consent**  
With your consent, we may share your personal information with third-party marketing partners for their own marketing purposes. We do not share your personal information with third parties for those third parties’ marketing purposes unless you opt-in to such sharing at the time you provide your personal information. **** If you do agree to have your personal information shared, your personal information will be disclosed to such third party(s) and all information you disclose will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy policies and practices of such third party(s) prior to agreeing to receive such information from third party(s). If you later decide that you no longer want to receive communication from a third party, you will need to contact that third party directly 

**Production partners and other third parties providing services on our behalf**  
We may share personal information with production partners and other third parties performing functions on our behalf; examples include vetting potential guests for The Doctors Show, hosting or operating the Web Site, sending e-mail and/or other communications, providing wireless services, removing repetitive information from customer lists, data analysis, marketing assistance, and customer service. These third parties may have access to your personal information for the purpose of performing such functions on our behalf.

 **Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions**  
When you choose to enter a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion, and in accordance with the terms and conditions of the promotion, your information may be disclosed to our sponsors and third parties who help design, administer and implement the promotion, including in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment and aggregated data analysis. Your information also may be disclosed as required by law, such as on a winners list. Also, by entering a promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the promotion.

 **Business Transfers**  
We may share your information, including personal information, in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of Web Site or Company, a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, and including any due diligence process.

 **Co-Branded Partners**  
Co-Branded Partners are third parties with whom we may jointly offer a service or feature. You can tell when you are accessing a service or feature offered by a Co-Branded Partner because the Co-Branded Partner's name will be featured prominently. You may be asked to provide information about yourself to register for a service offered by a Co-Branded Partner. In doing so, you may be providing your information to both us and the Co-Branded Partner, or we may share your information with the Co-Branded Partner. Please note that the Co-Branded Partner's privacy policy may also apply to its use of your information.

 **Legal Protections and Law Enforcement**  
We may disclose information about our users, including personal information, to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, and other law enforcement measures (e.g., at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation); and to comply with other legal obligations. We may also use device identifiers to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, internet service providers, wireless service providers or law enforcement agencies in our discretion. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.

 **Protection of Our Web Site and Users**  
We may disclose information to protect and defend the legal rights, interests, and safety of us and our partners and their employees, agents, and contractors (including enforcing our agreements), and to protect the safety and security of users of the Web Site and members of the public.

Non-Personal Information  
We may share non-personal information, such as aggregate user statistics, demographic information, and web site usage information with third parties in our discretion. 

Return to Top

 _ **THIRD-PARTY AD SERVING & AUDIENCE AND TRAFFIC MEASUREMENT SERVICES **_

******The Web Site works with network advertisers, ad agencies, analytics service providers, and other third parties to serve third-party advertisements on the Web Site, to serve our advertisements elsewhere online, and to provide us with information regarding use of and traffic on the Web Site (including without limitation the pages viewed and the actions users take when visiting the Web Site) and the effectiveness of our advertisements. The advertisements you see may be served by one or more third parties, who may use information about your activities on the Web Site, and other web sites and services you visit, over time and across the various devices you use, to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. One of the third parties with whom we work is CBS Interactive, which is primarily responsible for the advertising on the Web Site.   You can review CBS Interactive’s privacy policy at [www.cbsinteractive.com/legal/cbsi/privacy-policy](http://www.cbsinteractive.com/legal/cbsi/privacy-policy). ******

******Our service providers may collect certain information about your visits to and activity on the Web Site and other websites and services and may use this information to target advertising to you. These third parties may collect information through their owncookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies, and may otherwise collect or have access to information about you (such as usage information and device identifier), in an effort to understand your interests and deliver advertisements that are tailored to your interests. Some of these parties may collect personal information over time when you visit the Web Site or other online websites and services ******

******Cookies and web beacons, including without limitation those set by third-party network advertisers, may be used to (among other things): target advertisements, prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times, and conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you.******

 ** ** **We do not have access to the information these third parties may collect about your interests to deliver relevant advertising to you, and the information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy. However, as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may share certain non-personal information such as device identifiers, usage information and other de-identified information, including sharing with our third-party advertising companies, analytics providers and other vendors for advertising and analytics purposes.******

 ** ** **We use a variety of service providers to perform advertising and analytics services. Some of these companies may offer you a way to choose not to have your information used for advertising purposes.******

  *  ** ** **You may learn more about opting out of certain information use practices by CBS Interactive by visiting www.cbsinteractive.com/legal/cbsi/privacy-policy/business-partner-ad-opt-out.******
  * ******In addition, some of these companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”), which offers a single location to opt out of receiving tailored ads from member companies. To opt out of information collection by NAI member companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please visit the NAI consumer[opt out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).******
  * ******Also, through the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), several media and marketing associations have developed an industry self-regulatory program to give consumers a better understanding of and greater control over ads that are customized based on their online behavior across different Web Sites. To learn more and make choices about interest-based ads from participating third parties, please visit the DAA consumer[opt out page](http://optout.aboutads.info/).******
  * ******We use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of the Web Site and report on activities and trends. This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps, and online resources. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to[ www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/), and opt out of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).  ******
  * ******Third-party market research services, such as Nielsen, may access information about you through your social networking services. You can prevent Nielsen from receiving any data from Facebook that includes information identifying you by opting out of Nielsen measurement. Please click[here](https://www.facebook.com/help/769828729705201) to read about Facebook’s participation in Nielsen’s measurement services. Please click [here](http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy) for more information about Nielsen digital measurement products and [here](http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy#choice) to learn how to opt out of Nielsen measurement services. ******

******If you opt out of having your information used to deliver advertisements tailored to your interests, you will continue to see advertisements on our Web Site, but these advertisements may not be as relevant to you. These online advertising efforts on the Web Site do not result in you seeing more advertisements, just more relevant advertising, and they allow us to provide you with free content and services. We hope you value our efforts to show you content and advertising that more closely reflects your interests.******

 ** ** **Some of these advertising and analytics providers may, through the use of cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies on the Web Site, have access to information about the content viewed by Web Site users – including video content.   For more information, please see our Video Services [Policy](https://legalterms.cbsinteractive.com/video-services).******

 ** ** **Return to Top******

 _ **UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION AND OPTING OUT OF EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS**_  
 ** ** **The Web Site may contain web pages through which you can correct or update some of the personal information you have provided to us through registration with the Web Site or through which you may be able to unsubscribe from or modify the marketing emails or similar communications from the Web Site. We will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. If you have made any public posting, such as in a Public Area, these communications generally will not be removed. With regard to marketing emails and similar communications you may receive from us, you may tell us you no longer want to receive these emails from the Web Site by following the opt-out instructions provided to you in those communications. Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your account or use of the Web Site, such as administrative and services announcements and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you choose to opt-out from marketing communications.******

 ** ** **Return to Top******

 _ **SOCIAL NETWORKING SERVICES**_

 ** ** **We may offer you the ability to use certain third-party social networking services through the Web Site. For example, you can use third-party social networking services, such as Facebook or Twitter, to share information about your experience on the Web Site with your friends and followers on those services. These social networking services may be able to collect information about you, including about your activities on the Web Site, and they also may notify your friends on their services that you are a Web Site user or about your use of the Web Site, in accordance with their own privacy policies.****** ** ** ** ******

 ** ** **By using third-party social networking services through the Web Site, you consent to share information about you, including video content that you have watched on the Web Site, with your friends and followers on those services. (Please see our Video Services[Policy](https://legalterms.cbsinteractive.com/video-services) for more information on sharing of video content information with social networking services.) You may be able to limit how a third-party social networking service shares your information by visiting your social networking service’s website and updating your privacy settings.******

 _ **IMPORTANT NOTICE REGARDING PUBLIC AREAS OF THE WEB SITE AND USER CONTENT**_

 ** ** **The Web Site may provide features that allow or enable you to create a public profile which may include information such as your photo, name, contact information, and other information that you choose to post publicly ("Profile").******

 ** ** **The Web Site may contain public areas to which you can contribute your original text and audio or video content, such as comments, message boards, blog comments areas, personal blogs, online chat features, and any public portion of your Profile (collectively, "Public Areas"). If you submit comments, message board posts, votes, reviews, suggestions, chat messages, photographs, videos, audio recordings, music, text or other content ("User Content") to Public Areas, it may be published online or offline in any media or format (currently existing or later developed). Note that comment and review features, as well as other Public Areas, may be offered and controlled by third parties. Other users of the Web Site will have access to your User Content that is posted on the Web Site and may have the ability to share it with third parties across the Internet, including through the use of Web Site features allowing users to share links to User Content with third party web sites (such as Facebook, Twitter and similar sites). Company may use your User Content, or any portion of your User Content, that you submit to be published on the Web Site, whether directly to us or through a third party, for advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities. For the full terms and conditions regarding User Content you submit to the Web Site, please review the Web Site's Terms of[Use](https://www.thedoctorstv.com/terms-of-use).******

 ** ** **If you submit any User Content to Company or to a third party offering features on the Web Site, that User Content may be published online or offline (including, without limitation, on The Doctors Show, on a CD or DVD, or any other electronic or non-electronic media or format currently existing or later developed), we and our service providers, as well as any third party to whom you submit the User Content, may publish your name, voice, likeness and other personal information in connection with publishing the User Content or any portion thereof, and may use the User Content and any excerpt thereof in connection with advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities. For the full terms and conditions regarding User Content, please review the Web Site's Terms of[Use](https://www.thedoctorstv.com/terms-of-use).******

 ** ** **You also may have the ability to interact and communicate other members on the Web Site. Please use caution when interacting and communicating with people that you do not know personally. Please note that Company cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Therefore, use caution when including personal information in User Content or a Public Area or any message that you send using the Web Site or electing to personal information in your Profile viewable to other members.   ******

******Return to Top******

 _ **THIRD-PARTY CONTENT AND LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES**_  
 ** ** **Certain content on the Web Site (such as advertisements) may be hosted and served by third parties.  In addition, please note that the Web Site may contain links to other websites and services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites, and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of each website that you visit. When you select a link to a third-party web site from our Web Site (e.g., if you click through a banner advertisement), you will be leaving the Web Site. Any information that you disclose on the third-party website will be governed by that website's privacy policy******

 ** ** **Return to Top******

 _ **CONSENT TO TRANSFER**_ ** **  
 ** ** ** **The Web Site is operated in the United States and we do not intend to collect Personal Information from users residing outside the United States or Canada. If you are located outside of the United States (including, without limitation, within the European Union), please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using the Web Site or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen, and you agree that the laws of the United States and the State of California will apply.********

 ** ** ** **Return to Top********

 ** _ **PROTECTION OF INFORMATION**_**  
 ** ** ** **We have adopted commercially reasonable technical, administrative, and physical procedures to help protect your information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, and alteration. Please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.********

 ** ** ** **Return to Top********

 ** ** _ **A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY**_****  
 ** ** ** ** **The Web Site is a general audience web site. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children younger than the age of thirteen (13) on the Web Site and we will delete any information later determined to be from a user younger than thirteen (13).**********

 ** ** ** ** **Return to Top**********

 ** ** _ **NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES AND YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY**_****  
 ** ** ** ** **By using the Web Site, you acknowledge your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. From time to time, Company may update this Privacy Policy. However, Company will use your personal information in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time you submitted the information, unless you consent to the new or revised policy.**********

 ** ** ** ** **Return to Top**********

 _ **CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS – YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**_  
 ** ** ** ** **Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, residents of the State of California have the right to request certain information from companies conducting business in California relating to third parties to which the company has disclosed certain categories of personal information during the preceding year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that a company may comply, as we do, by disclosing in its privacy policy that it provides consumers a choice (opt-out or opt-in) regarding sharing personal information with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes, and information on how to exercise that choice.   As stated above in this Privacy Policy, Company provides you a choice prior to sharing your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you do not opt-in at the time Company offers that choice, Company does not share your information with that identified third party for its direct marketing purposes.**********

 ** ** **If you are a California resident and you have questions about our practices with respect to sharing information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes and your ability to exercise choice, please send your request by email to thedoctors-legal@drphil.com or write to us at  Stage 29 Productions, LLC, Attn: Legal, 2401 Colorado Avenue, Suite 500E, Santa Monica, CA 90404-3585. You must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your e-mail or include it in your writing if you choose to write to us at the designated mailing address. You must include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.******

 ** ** ** ** **Return to Top**********

 _ **CANADIAN RESIDENTS**_  
 ** ** ** ** **This Privacy Policy complies with the requirements of the _Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act_ (PIPEDA). Under Canadian law, you have a right to access any personal information we hold about you. You may ask us to access and/or correct your information by emailing us at thedoctors-legal@drphil.com or writing to us at Stage 29 Productions, LLC, Attn: Legal, 2401 Colorado Avenue, Suite 500E, Santa Monica, CA 90404-3585. Please note that we may require you to send us proof of your identity before providing you with access to your personal information. If you send us a request to access or correct information, then we will contact you within 30 days (although it may take us longer to fully respond to your request). If you are not satisfied with our response to your query or complaint, you may also contact the Privacy Commissioner of Canada.**********

 ** ** **As our privacy policy makes clear, we may share information with third parties, such as co-branded partners and authorized third parties. However, we will only share your information with such parties where we have your express or implied consent to do so. If you object to our sharing your information with such parties, or if you do not wish to receive marketing communications (such as emails) from us, then you may contact us to let us know your objection at any time.******

 ** ** ** ** **Return to Top**********
